

Marc Partensky

• 46 rue d'Avron, Paris, 75020, France

12/01/2000

marc.partensky@gmail.com

07 67 44 36 62

√
08 12/01/2000

√
09 67 44 36 62

√
09 67 44 36 62

√
09 67 67 44 36 62

√
09 67 67 44 36 62

√
09 67 67 44 36 62

√
09 67 67 67 67 67

√
09 67 67 67

√
09 67 67

√
09 67 67

√
09 67

√
09 67

√
09 67

√
09 67

√
09 67

√
09 67

√
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

✓
09 67

https://marcpartensky.com

in marc-partensky

marcpartensky

After 3 years of professional experience as an apprentice at Pickup Services and then at BNP Paribas, and as a former student at ISEP in alternation with BNP Paribas, I am seeking a permanent position in the field of artificial intelligence or application development. My professional profile is backed by a strong experience in projects available on GitHub at https://github.com/MarcPartensky and my personal website at https://marcpartensky.com. Focused in the field of DevOps, I am committed to bringing my skills and creativity to a stimulating professional environment.

EDUCATION

Institut Supérieur d'Électronique de Paris (09/01/2020 - 09/03/2023)

Diplôme d'Ingénieur, École d'Ingénieur du Numérique

Transport and Telecommunication Institute (01/02/2023 - 28/05/2023)

Moblilité Internationale à Riga en Lettonie, École d'Ingénieur

Institut Supérieur d'Électronique de Paris (01/09/2018 - 30/09/2020)

Filières MPSI / PSI, Classes Préparatoires associés à Stanislas

Saint Jean-Hulst (01/09/2015 - 01/09/2018)

Baccalauréat Généraliste - Spécialité Mathématiques

WORK EXPERIENCE

BNP Paribas - 1st European bank, 8th largest banking group worldwide

Data Analyst - Apprenticeship

(23/08/2022 - 30/09/2023)

- Implementation of interactive and intuitive dashboards using Tableau Software suite, enabling the implementation of ITIL methodology for IT Group Production governance.
- Utilization of modern data manipulation methods such as Data Wrangling and Data Mining to achieve agile data extraction, efficient data cleaning, and transformation.
- https://bnpparibas.fr

Pickup Services - subsidiary of the french group La Poste, a leading provider of out-of-home delivery services in France

(16/12/2020 - 06/01/2022)

Software Developer - Apprenticeship

- Implementations of features enabling the simulation of parcels in the information system to ensure their proper delivery using the AspNet.Core stack in C#, React in JavaScript, MongoDB, and RabbitMQ.
- Development of batch management tools in C# to dynamically load translations of a React application from a MongoDB database.
- https://pickup.fr

Numéris - Association helping students through paid assignments

(01/09/2022 - 30/06/2023)

Technical Chief Officer

- Software and application development of the website enabling student registration for missions explored by Numéris, utilizing Laravel,
 Angular, Docker, Caddy, and Github Actions technologies.
- https://numeris-isep.fr

Junior ISEP - top 3 Junior Enterprises in France with a revenue of 200k, composed of 40 students

(01/04/2021 - 30/06/2022)

Technical Officer

- Technical and functional administration of the entire IS based on Proxmox, Docker, Ldap, Pritunl, Pihole, Gitlab, Edge Router.
- Development of an ERP using the Spring Boot, React, and PostgreSQL stack, and a CRM equipped with Symfony, React, and PostgreSQL.
- Technical validation of commercial proposals, estimation, and technical monitoring of client projects.
- https://juniorisep.com

SKILLS Python **Javascript** C++ C# 0000 0000 **PHP** React Java Bash 0000 0000 0000 **NestJS NodeJS** ASP.Net SOL **•••**00 Linux MySQL **PostgreSQL** MongoDB 0000 0000 0000 Docker **Docker Swarm** Traefik Wordpress ElasticSearch Modèle OSI MVC **Deep Learning** • • • • • • • • • • • • •••00 **Hashicorp Vault** Tableau Desktop **LANGUAGES English** Professionnal 0000 INTERESTS **FinTech Arch Linux Deepl Learning** Scuba Diving CMAS 2* **DevOps AWARDS** Hackathon - Green Code (08/10/2022)ISFP Winner of the team coding prize among 71 students. https://www.isep.fr/blog/event/hackathon-green-code/ Hackathon - ANFR (20/11/2022)**ISEP** Second place in a team of 3 among 25 students. https://hackathon.anfr.fr/ CERTIFICATIONS **Neural Networks and Deep Learning** (24/03/2020)https://coursera.org/verify/85SDPU4SWDQM Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization (03/03/2020)Coursera https://coursera.org/verify/GCQZS7H8HFM4 Structuring Machine Learning Projects (05/04/2020)Coursera http://coursera.org/verify/G52ATN4KSM69 Convolutional Neural Networks (04/12/2020)Coursera http://coursera.org/verify/C76NP3CMBMB3 Sequence Models (29/04/2020)Coursera, Deep learning http://coursera.org/verify/23X8YKXP69CZ